Ok, who would like to start?
May be I will start with a question.
Do you know who is the current biggest user of 3d printers in the industry?
If people have interest in playing with these printers and you do not have couple thousand euros laying around.
Do you know about community where they can try these things out?
I heard that there are some projects or possibilities to print your own printer.
What is your opinion about this one?
What is the real advantage for a private person like everyone to have its own.
Because if you buy it, you pay 25k, 50k czech couwns for a printer.
And what do you print? One cup for coffee, case for your iPhone and then?
What do you do with it?
And one other question to this.
For Deutsche Boerse. How could you use that in the company?
It should more fun for facility management ;-)
I would like to just add that the innovators or inovating it's not directly related to our industry.
It's about innovating everything.
It's about exploring.
It's about thinking in different way then usuall.
May be it's not related to financial industry as such, but you can create amazing things.
You can create something new. You can start next big thing.
Do you have another question?
So you think this has a future?
It's going to become next big thing?
Some time soon?
This is a question more to Marek, but I would say yes.
I can print a house with a 3d printer.
In China there are some experiments how to do it in one day.
What is power consumption of your printer?
It means that one day of printing is like 100 crowns per electricity?
You have mentioned it buing few materials you can use it with that particular printer.
Can you somehow as I seen it on TV printing chocolate, printing food?
Can you adjust that specific printer to print chocolate?